前提回顾就不翻译啦
Previously on Sons
of Anarchy...
NERO: You trying this in the court
of public opinion, Counselor?
PATTERSON: I have no control of what the
press gets ahold of or how they spin it.
NERO: - Right.
PATTERSON: - Giving up the Sons
of Anarchy is going to be a very
popular get-out-of-jail-free card.
GEMMA: What are you
doing with Lowen?
You divorcing Jax? You planning
on some kind of custody coup?
TARA: What I do with my family
is none of your business.
GEMMA: Bitch!
(Tara screams)
- Jesus!
UNSER: - What the hell?
TARA: My baby!
Look what you did.
GEMMA: - Oh, I didn't do that.
MARGARET: - Yes, you did.
We all saw it. Take
her out of here.
TARA: What are you
gonna do about Gemma?
JAX: Restraining order keeps her
away from you and the boys.
UNSER: It breaks my heart that
you had to become something
so wrong to do what you
thought was right.
TARA: I did it to
protect my kids, Wayne.
UNSER: I can't help you no more.
ELIAS: - Need anything, friend?
CLAY: - Yeah, maybe.
ELIAS: I think you'll like this one.
It gets real good around page 47.
JAX: What's going on?
BAROSKY: Patterson pulled me
into her office this morning.
JAX: About the headline?
BAROSKY: She's crushing me, kid;
she's threatening to bring in
the sheriffs to police
the port, and that steps
on everybody's game.
NERO: I'm ready to give up
the source of the KG-9.
It wasn't Teller who
supplied the gun.
It was me. I'm responsible for
the death of those children.
PATTERSON: If you cared about these kids,
you'd tell me everything-- the whole truth.
NERO: I don't know where
you're going with this, but I
ain't saying another word
to you without my lawyer.
PATTERSON: You don't
need a lawyer.
Toric killed Erin Byrne.
He's free to go.
JAX: Do you ever regret
it-- coming back?
TARA: A lot of things
I'd do differently.
JAX: I just feel so far
away from you now.
Please let me back in.
♪
(baby crying)
(birds squawking quietly)
(Gemma sighs)
早上好
NERO: Good morning.
嗯
Mmm.
真高兴你回来了
GEMMA: I'm so glad you're home.
我也是
NERO: Me, too.
我去煮点咖啡
GEMMA: I'll make
you some coffee.
(refrigerator door closes)
谢谢
TARA: Thank you.
哦
Oh.
(paper ruffles)
希望我们今天没有上头条
GEMMA: Hopefully we didn't
make the front page today.
没有
NERO: Nope.
看上去没有
Doesn't look like it.
我的15分钟好像到了
Guess my 15 minutes are up.
我有个自己的头条新闻告诉你
GEMMA: I got my own
headline you need to hear.
你昨晚刚回到家
Didn't want to tell you last
当时不想告诉你
night, step on the homecoming.
值得上头条的事情?
NERO: Front-page-type stuff?
怎么了
What's going on?
是我和Tara之间的事情
GEMMA: It's me and Tara.
糟透了
Shit happened.
你确定要告诉我这些?
TARA: Are you sure you want
to tell me all this?
是的
JAX: Yeah, I do.
Clay在监狱里没被杀是因为我们需要他
The reason Clay wasn't killed
inside is because we need him.
爱尔兰人希望他在加州卖枪
The Irish want him to be
point for guns here in Cali.
他们打算下周在他从监狱转移时
They're gonna take down his
把他救出来
transport next week,
bust him out.
天啊
TARA: Jesus Christ.
哇
NERO: Wow.
嗯 我知道
GEMMA: Yeah, I know.
老妈 这可不是件小事
NERO: That's some
crazy-ass shit, Mama.
你能证明这些吗
Can you prove any of it?
Wendy和Tara是一伙的
GEMMA: Wendy was in
on it with Tara.
她有些愧疚
Guilt got to her.
我觉得她会支持我
I think she'll back me up.
你是说一个父亲被他爱的女人
他儿子的母亲背叛
NERO: You're talking about a
father trying to wrap his brain
他会疯了的
around some seriously heinous betrayal by
the woman he loves, mother of his son.
我觉得必要找到更多证据而不只是
一个吸毒者的话
I think you might need more
than the word of a junkie.
特别是他恨的那个
Especially a junkie he hates.
我觉得你不应该再和我讲这些了
TARA: I don't think you
should tell me anything else.
我知道你在做你必须做的事情
JAX: I know you're doing
what you got to do.
和我保持距离 我明白
Putting distance between us.
I get it.
我整夜都在琢磨怎样让你摆脱指控 Tara
I spent all night trying to figure out how
to help you with these charges, Tara.
- 你没办法
- 是的
TARA: - You can't.
JAX: - Yeah.
但是作为丈夫我会遵守诺言
But I can keep my
promise as a husband.
说实话
To be honest.
之前没告诉过你
Which I haven't.
我一直在努力保护你
I've been trying to protect
you from everything,
但一直没有成功
which clearly hasn't worked.
一点也没有
At all.
现在我知道你在努力了 老妈
NERO: Now, I know
you're trying, Mama.
我现在的这些蠢事 不 不是你该承担的
The struggle that I'm having with this
shit, that-that ain't your burden.
谢谢你没有怀疑我
GEMMA: Thanks for
not doubting me.
或者至少你没让我看出来
Or for at least not
showing me that you do.
Gem 我知道你有秘密
NERO: You got some
heavy secrets, Gem.
我看得出
I see them.
也看得出对你的影响
I see the weight of them.
这些秘密让你变得不快乐
How they drain
the joy from you.
但是对于你的宝贝们
我知道你永远不会撒谎
But your babies... I know that you'd
never spin the truth about that.
我爱你
GEMMA: I love you.
我也是
TARA: Me, too.
你知道 自从你离开 Stockton
JAX: You know, since you
got out of Stockton,
你一直没说过 我爱你
you haven't been able
to say "I love you."
我知道这对你来说很难
I know that must
be hard for you.
对不起 我也不会对你说了
I'm sorry, I'll
stop telling you.
只想让你知道我的感受
Just know it's what I feel.
(Tara sighs)
♪ Riding through this world ♪
♪ all alone ♪
♪ God takes your soul ♪
♪ you're on your own ♪
♪ The crow flies straight ♪
♪ a perfect line ♪
♪ on the devil's bed ♪
♪ until you die ♪
♪ Gotta look this life ♪
♪ in the eye ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01 中文 Derekwxt
www.addic7ed.com
早上好
PATTERSON: Good morning.
- 中尉 我有些事要告诉你
- 是 长官
- I need to update you, Lieutenant.
ROOSEVELT: - Yes, ma'am.
说吧
Here we are.
我知道昨晚 Padilla 被释放了
I understand that Padilla
was released last night.
没错
PATTERSON: That's right.
她头发怎么了？
EGLEE: What happened
to her hair?
大姐要玩真的了
CANE: Sister be doing
it with the real flow.
啥意思？
EGLEE: I don't know
what that means.
我听说受害者的爸爸发生了什么事情
ROOSEVELT: I heard about what
happened to the victim's father.
在Stockton自杀了 没有记录
Suicide in Stockton.
Not from the papers.
我 我在Division大街和Alexander谈过了
I-I spoke to Alexander
at Division Street.
- 哦
- 很遗憾
PATTERSON: - Oh.
ROOSEVELT: - I'm sorry.
是啊 很遗憾
PATTERSON: Yeah, it's very sad.
我想我心里某些地方很感激
I guess a part of me is
grateful that something
这工作依然能给我惊喜
can still surprise me in this job.
说明我不是全部都石头做的
Makes me not completely
made of stone.
至少还不是
Yet.
我再给你调配3组人马
I'm giving you
three extra units.
我要让Jax全天被监视
I want 24/7 surveillance
on Jax Teller.
你觉得这是利用资源的最佳方式?
ROOSEVELT: You think that's really
the best use of our resources?
长官 我了解这些人
Ma'am, I know these guys.
上了头条之后 他们会像童子军一样乖
After those headlines,
they'll go total Boy Scout.
不会冒险做生意
Won't risk any business.
要坚持和耐心
PATTERSON: It's about
consistency and patience.
一旦我们对他们放松警惕了
The minute we ease up, turn our
backs, look the other way,
他们指不定会犯出什么事
that's the minute we allow
another tragedy to happen.
你对对他们严盯死守没疑问吧 中尉
You don't have a problem stepping hard
on these guys, do you, Lieutenant?
不 我没有
ROOSEVELT: No. I don't.
很好 监视马上开始
PATTERSON: Good. Surveillance
begins immediately.
一小时内给你增援
You'll have backup
within the hour.
(door opens, closes)
(blowing kazoo)
(Jax sighs)
窗户擦得不错 Chucky
JAX: Looking clean, Chucky.
谢谢
CHUCK (through kazoo):
Thank you.
这就是为什么你是个异类
JAX: And that's why
you're a freak.
兄弟 欢迎回来
Hey. Welcome back, my brother.
嗨 兄弟
HAPPY: Hey, buddy.
爱尔兰人那边怎么样
JAX: How'd the Irish
sales pitch go?
挺好的 和我们大部分的买家都接上头了
HAPPY: Good, man. Connected
with most of our buyers.
他们还想和Clay谈谈 但是似乎也想改变
They still want to talk to Clay,
but they seemed open to change.
他们明白我们为什么退出了
They get why we're
stepping away.
这就好
JAX: Good.
还没意大利人谈过
BOBBY: Couldn't get a
sit-down with the Italians.
我觉得他们队伍换血不会太顺利
I don't think the personnel change
is gonna land too well with them.
爱尔兰人在操作这件事
CHIBS: Irish are setting it up.
他们在监狱里有人给Clay了个电话
让他能联系外面
They got someone inside that's gonna get
a phone to Clay, have him reach out.
- 让所有的买家都停手
- 好的
- Lock down all the buyers.
JAX: - All right.
在他们联系Clay之后 你盯着所有人
You follow up with everyone
after they talk to Clay.
好
CHIBS: Aye.
(electronic doorbell chimes)
早
UNSER: Morning.
不好意思打扰你们了
Sorry to interrupt.
哇 你还没躺尸？
BOBBY: Wow. You didn't die yet?
每天趴下一点
UNSER: A little every day.
(men chuckling)
- 能见到你真好 长官
- 是啊 你也是 Bobby
BOBBY: - Good to see you, Chief.
UNSER: - Yeah, you, too, Bobby.
你需要什么 大队长
JAX: What do you
need, Cap-a-tain?
只想站用点你的时间 主席
UNSER: Just a minute of
your time there, Pres.
没问题
JAX: Yeah, okay.
麻烦各位了
UNSER: Excuse us, gentlemen.
- 我在楼上和你谈
- 可以 没问题
JAX: - I'll see you upstairs.
BOBBY: - Yeah, all right.
你要咖啡吗
JAX: Can I get you some coffee?
你有 呃 啤酒吗
UNSER: You got any,
uh, beer back there?
及时享乐了?
JAX: Miller time already?
终极病殃的早餐
UNSER: Breakfast of
terminally-ill champions.
坐下吧
JAX: Sit down.
我想让你知道
Hey, I wanted you to know.
Tara告诉我了 你对她和孩子们很照顾
Tara told me how good you've
been with her and the boys.
这些破事缠身 都没机会和你说谢谢
With all the shit going on,
haven't had a chance to say
但是真的很感激你能照顾他们
thank you, but appreciate
you looking out, man.
没事
UNSER: Yeah.
嗯 没问题
It's, uh, no problem.
你有一个好家庭 孩子
You got a real nice
family there, son.
是啊 一部分吧
JAX: Yeah, some of them.
也是
UNSER: Right.
我知道这也许不是我该管的事情 但是
I know it probably ain't none
of my business, but...
我认识你妈比谁都久
I know your mom longer than anybody.
我们还是孩子的时候在这吃饭撒欢
We used to dine and dash this
place when we were kids.
是啊 我也是
JAX: Yeah, me, too.
听着 我知道你关心我妈 Wayne
Look, I know you care
about my mom, Wayne.
- 不只是这样 孩子
- 天啊
UNSER: - It's not just that, son...
JAX: - Jesus Christ.
- 这是干什么?
UNSER: What the hell?
喂 你他妈在干嘛
JAX: Hey! What the
hell you doing?!
哇 哦
UNSER: Whoa... whoa!
哦 干什么呢这是
Oh! What the hell?!
喂
JAX: Hey!
(Chucky blowing kazoo sadly)
我的天啊
UNSER: Holy shit!
喂
JAX: Hey!
Hey!
喂
- 放开我
- 你谁啊
GIRL: - Let go of me!
JAX: - Who are you?
喂 你干嘛做这些啊
Hey! Why'd you do that?
强奸 强奸
GIRL: Rape! Rape!
真的要这样?
JAX: Seriously?
放开我 来人...帮...
GIRL: Let go of me! Somebody...
take...!
好吧 好吧
JAX: All right! All right!
(people murmuring)
怎么了这是
MAN: What's that all about?
你应该拿好你的枪骑车快走
MAN 2: You need to take your guns
and your loud bikes and just go.
你们都该离开这儿
WOMAN: You all need
to get out of here.
- 欢迎
- 谢谢
INMATE: - Welcome.
CLAY: - Thanks.
- 谢谢你能来
INMATE: Thanks for coming.
- 欢迎 进来吧
PREACHER: Welcome. Come on in.
你好
INMATE: How you doing?
欢迎 欢迎
PREACHER: Welcome. Welcome.
你来了真好 快进来
Good to see you. Good.
Come on in.
很好
Good.
(door closes)
我想谢谢你们今天的到来 先生们
I'd like to thank you all,
gentlemen, for coming today.
很明智的选择
You made the right choice.
今天我们读约翰书8:32 真相的力量(圣经)
Today's reading is from John
8:32 on power of truth.
请你们翻开圣经
Will you all now please
open your Bibles.
他是Gary Putner的孩子
UNSER: It was Gary Putner's kid.
他12岁就开始进出少年监狱和康复教育
She's been in and out of juvie
and rehab since she was 12.
是有些问题
Got a few problems.
是啊 她用了一个扳手来解决问题
JAX: Yeah. She's working
them out with a pipe wrench.
为什么是我的车
TIG: Why my bike?
我说 真的吗 每个青少年女孩子都恨我
I mean, really? Do all
teenage girls just hate me?
- 对
- 没错
JAX: - Yes.
CHIBS: - Yep.
(men chuckling)
哦 好的吧
TIG: Oh. Yeah.
- 有人认识这个叫Putner的吗
- Clay也许认识
JAX: - We know this Putner guy?
UNSER: - Clay might have.
在他给Oswald工作之前是个机械师
He was a journeyman mechanic
before he went to work for Oswald.
他在作坊那当领班
He's an equipment
foreman at the mill.
好吧 但是我们从来没和他打过交道
BOBBY: Yeah, but we never had
a beef with the guy--
- 至少我记得没有
- 没妈妈?
- not that I can remember.
CHIBS: - No mother?
她死了 交通事故
UNSER: She was killed.
Car accident.
18号高速公路 刚生下孩子
Highway 18, just after
the kid was born.
这可能说明了些问题
That might be the connection.
是拖车引起的连带事故
It was the pile-up caused by the
tractor-trailer,
击中你爸之后 她被切断了
jackknifed after it hit your dad.
所以她把他妈妈的死算在了我们的头上
JAX: So she blames us
for her mother's death.
过了18年之后?
BOBBY: 18 years later?
不知道啊 有人默哀的方式很奇特
UNSER: I don't know. People
grieve in strange ways.
- 啊 该死
- 他们来这是因为那个女孩?
JUICE: - Ah, shit.
- Think they're here 'cause of the girl?
想让我打探一下吗
UNSER: Want me to go find out?
不用 我来好了
JAX: No, I got it.
(electronic doorbell chimes)
早
Morning.
ROOSEVELT: Yeah.
这发生什么了
What happened there?
不知道啊
JAX: I don't know.
很明显 有些人不喜欢冰激凌
Clearly someone doesn't
like ice cream.
非常不喜欢 乳糖不耐症是吗
ROOSEVELT: Extremely
lactose intolerant, huh?
- 对 就是这个
- 嗯
JAX: - That's right.
ROOSEVELT: - Hmm.
我猜你不是为了我的破窗户才来的吧
JAX: Guessing you're not
here about my broken window.
的确 我不是
ROOSEVELT: No, I'm not.
这段时间有人会跟着你们
You're gonna have a shadow
for a little while.
不是我决定的
It's not my call.
Patterson?
JAX: Patterson?
她在找枪的来源
ROOSEVELT: She's looking
for the gun source,
而且她只有一个怀疑对象
and she only has
one suspect on her list.
好吧
JAX: Okay.
跟踪是板上钉了
ROOSEVELT: This tail
is gonna happen.
别搞破坏了 好不
Let's not make it
ugly, all right?
- 不会 我明白
- 那就好
JAX: - No, I get it.
ROOSEVELT: - All right.
伙计们
Fellas.
妈的
BOBBY: Shit.
(cell phone ringing)
我们的新尾巴
JAX: Our new tail.
这可不好 Jackie
CHIBS: This is bad, Jackie.
未来一周我们可是会非常忙
We got a very, very
busy week ahead of us.
我知道
JAX: I know.
我们要把刚才的谈话完结了
UNSER: We need to finish
that conversation.
会的
JAX: We will.
好吧 是Barosky
JUICE: All right. It's Barosky.
他说很紧急
Says it's urgent.
嗯 他必须来找我们
JAX: Well, he's gonna
have to come to us.
在Diosa
Diosa.
听到了没 来Diosa
JUICE: You heard him? Diosa.
好 Clay有消息告诉我
JAX: All right, keep
me updated on Clay.
- 你和Juice去找那女孩
- 好
- You and Juice, find the girl.
CHIBS: - Yeah.
我们去会会 Dirty Charlie
JAX: And let's go
see Dirty Charlie.
Hap 跟我们走
Hap, come with us.
工资已经移到另一个账户了
LOWEN: Salaried income has been
shifted into a new account.
很好
TARA: Good.
现金呢
LOWEN: What about the cash?
保险箱在你们名下
Safety deposit box is
in both your names.
现金是他的
TARA: Cash is his.
这些是为了离开他而不是赶走他
It's about getting away,
not cleaning him out.
这个是目击者名单
LOWEN: Here's a list of
character witnesses.
还能想起谁来吗
Anyone else you can think of?
这单子真短
TARA: That's a short list.
不要紧 可以的
No, it's fine.
我看了下医院记录
LOWEN: I looked over your medical
documentation--
怀孕可能行 流产 医生签名
positive pregnancy, ultrasounds,
doctor's signatures...
全是Margaret Murphy催促的
all expedited...
by Margaret Murphy.
用假的医疗记录来获取抚养权可是重罪
Using false medical records to
substantiate a custody hold is a felony.
我知道
TARA: I know that.
还有两周就要出庭了
LOWEN: We're two weeks away from
standing in front of a jury.
如果你还在策划些别的事情 我现在需要知道
If there's any more drama you've
got planned, I need to know now.
我都告诉你了
TARA: You know everything.
耶稣对信奉他的犹太人说
PREACHER: So Jesus said to the
Jews who believed Him,
如果你们遵守我的话 就是我真正的信徒
"If you abide in my Word, you
are truly my disciples.
你们会知道真理 真想让你们获得自由
You will know the truth and
this truth will set you free."
明白么 约翰他不是在说你们的真理
或者是我的真理
See, John-- he ain't talking
about your truth or my truth,
- 他说的是上帝的真理
- 阿门
- he's talking about God's truth.
INMATE: - Amen.
作为一般人 我们不知道真正的真理
PREACHER: As mortal men,
we can't know real truth.
为什么呢? 因为我们说谎吗
And why? Is it
because we are liars?
因为我们邪恶或者不可信吗 不是
Is it because we are evil
or untrustworthy? No.
我们有人类的真理 因为我们生来就有罪
We have the truth of man because
we were born with the sin of man!
兄弟们 是罪恶蒙蔽我们 不让我们
认识上帝和他的真理
It is sin, my brothers, that keeps
us from knowing God and His truth!
- 没错
- 罪恶
INMATE: - That's right.
PREACHER: - Sin!
我们都带着这肮脏的眼镜
Those dirty glasses
that we all wear.
是我们所说的所做的都为自己着想
It is what makes everything we say,
everything we do, self-motivated!
那么怎样才能了解上帝的真理
So how do we get to
know God and His truth?
怎样克服自己的欲望
How do we see beyond our
own selfish desires?
怎样获取自由
How do we set ourselves free?
上帝
Jesus.
阿门 上帝
CLAY: Amen, Jesus.
Amen, Jesus!
(chuckles)
让我直说吧 神父
Let me get something
straight, Rev.
某个犹太人被定在了十字架上
Some Jew gets nailed to a
cross, like, uh, I don't know,
谁他妈知道在一千年之前 他就成了
a thousand who-gives-a-shit
years ago, and he's gonna
能给我们这些人渣带来快乐和自由的良药?
be the magic pill that pulls all of
us scumbags to happiness and freedom?
是的 就是这样 我的兄弟
PREACHER: Yes, it
will, my brother.
哇
(Clay chuckles) CLAY: Wow.
Wow!
你知道上帝给我什么了吗
You know what God
gave me, brother?
你知道什么让我自由了吗
You know what sets me free?
逼（这段直翻了...)
Pussy.
(laughter)
甜蜜神圣的逼
Sweet, holy pussy.
知道吗 上帝制造男人只有三个理由
You see, God, He put man on
this planet for three reasons,
吃喝 战斗
eating... fighting...
还有 操翻紧实湿润的逼
and
tearing up tight, wet pussy!
够了 犯人
GUARD: That's enough, inmate!
这个 这个擦干净了我的黑色眼睛 兄弟
CLAY: That... that is what cleans
my dark glasses, my brother.
闭嘴坐下 Clay
GUARD: Shut up and
sit down, Morrow.
我做不下来 上帝在我身体里
CLAY: I can't sit!
I got the Lord in me!
他想让我站着 想让我传道
He wants me up,
He wants me preaching,
他想让我传播信条
He wants me to spread the gospel...
逼是治愈者 逼是救世主
pussy the healer,
pussy the redeemer--
我能为了逼阿门吗
Can I get a "Amen" for pussy!
走吧 快出去 混蛋
GUARD 2: Let's go. You're
out of here, asshole!
(clamoring, guard screaming)
(Clay spits)
我现在闻到真理了 兄弟
CLAY: I "nose" the
truth now, brother!
(guard continues screaming)
我自由了 香甜的逼给了我自由
I'm free. Sweet pussy
has set me free!
(cackling)
- 嗨
JAX: - Hey.
NERO: - Hey.
- 你回来了真好 兄弟
JAX: Glad you're back, brother.
谢谢 兄弟 见到你真好
NERO: Thanks, mano.
Good to see you.
我们知道那都是诬陷
BOBBY: We knew it
was all bullshit.
对 你们知道 正义胜过一切 对吧
NERO: Yeah, you know,
justice prevails, right?
在Barosky过来捣乱之前我们要聊一下
We need to catch up before Barosky
comes over here, ruins our day.
- 家事
- 好 没问题
- Family thing.
JAX: - Yeah. Sure.
我希望是你家里的事
I'm hoping it's your family
you need to talk about.
Gemma 现在也是家里人了
NERO: Gemma is my
family now, mano.
嗯 很好 因为我不管她了
JAX: Well, that's good, 'cause
I'm about done with her.
嗯 我看出来了
NERO: Yeah, I'm seeing that.
听着 我 我知道这很糟
Look, I... I know
how bad this feels.
但是我觉得你应该回顾一下 再想想这件事
But I think that you should go back
take another look at what happened.
查查真相 Jax
Find the truth in
all of this, Jax.
我知道真相 Nero
JAX: I already know
the truth, Nero!
- 不 不
- 什么
NERO: - No... no...
JAX: - What?
- 你说我老婆骗人
- 哇哦
- You think my wife is a liar?
NERO: - Whoa!
我是说 事情比你想的要复杂
I'm just saying it's a lot more
complicated, bro, than you...
听着 我明白了
JAX: Look, I get it.
你爱上我老妈了 你为她说话
You're in love with my mom,
you're staying in her corner,
这是你的自由
that's your choice.
但是如果我们之间还做生意
But if we're going to keep doing
business together,
我和我家里的破事不归你管
the shit that went down between
me and my family is off-limits.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
以后别再和我谈起这件事
This conversation
doesn't happen again.
和别人也不行
With anyone.
Jax
NERO: Jax...
老大 Charlie和火辣女士来了
HAPPY: Boss... Charlie
and the MILF madame are here.
好
JAX: All right.
去吧 合伙人
NERO: Let's go, partner.
- 你见过Bobby了
- 是的
JAX: - I see you met Bobby.
COLETTE: - Yes.
很高兴你带顾问来了
BAROSKY: Glad you
brought the think tank.
你或许需要他们 你来付保释金?
We may need them.
You pull bail?
他们没证据 只能让我走了
NERO: They had nothing.
Had to let me go.
你真够幸运的
BAROSKY: Good for you.
你自由了我被关禁闭了
While you were getting freed
up, I was getting shut down.
来自区检察官的暴力指控
Health violations, compliments
of our district attorney.
我以为你会用受害人老爸的自杀作为筹码
JAX: I thought you were gonna use
the victim's dad fubar as leverage.
那个死婊子通过别的事找我们麻烦
BAROSKY: That pitch bitch is
coming at us sideways,
还有我证明不了那人的死和她有关
and I can't prove she had
anything to do with that.
我们没通过护送服务
COLETTE: We didn't make the
escort rating, either-- denied.
不明原因
Unspecified reasons.
没有Diosa分部了
No Diosa Del Sur.
该死
JAX: Goddamn.
她想让你为学校枪击负责 兄弟
BAROSKY: She wants you for
that school shooting, man.
她还会死盯着和你一起的人
And she's gonna continue to
strangle everybody in bed with you.
听着 孩子 我不是奸细也不是圣人
Now, listen, kid, I ain't no rat
but I ain't no martyr, either.
(Jax sighs)
- 我会有办法的
- 什么办法 Jax
JAX: - I'll figure it out.
COLETTE: - How, Jax?
听着 Patterson她绝望了 她没证据
NERO: Look, Patterson-- she's
desperate; she got nothing.
她会撤销这些玩意儿 我们只要等着就行
She's gonna move off of all this shit.
We just got to wait it out.
对 你们必须等 但要在Stockton外面
BAROSKY: No, you got to wait.
Out of Stockton.
对不起 但是这个我承受不起 我撤了
I'm sorry, but I can't take the hit.
I got to eject.
代我向帅脸Jack和帮会说再见
Say so long to Handsome
Jack and the biker brigade.
别这样 Charlie Nero说得对
JAX: Come on, Charlie.
Nero's right.
这就是Patterson想要的
This is exactly what
Patterson wants--
想伤害我们 因为她没证据
to hurt us 'cause she's got no case.
我知道 孩子 我知道 但现在这也是我想要的
BAROSKY: I know, kid, I know.
But right now, it's what I want, too.
听着 对不起
Now, look, I'm sorry.
世道有变 告诉我
Things change, you let me know.
走吧
Let's go.
(door opens)
(door closes)
我不知道他在这
GEMMA: Didn't know he
was gonna be here.
老妈 我们也许应该去摄影棚
NERO: Mama, maybe we
should go into the studio...
没事 我要走了
JAX: Don't bother. I'm leaving.
只是别让他干你的脏活
Just don't send him to
do your dirty work.
没人让我做任何事
NERO: Nobody sent
me to do anything.
我只是想帮忙
I was just trying to help.
别对他发火
GEMMA: Don't take it out on him.
好 我觉得他更了解了
JAX: Yeah, well, I think
he knows better now.
真可惜你不了解
GEMMA: Too bad you don't.
你知道他为了你和帮会做了什么吗
You have any idea what he just
did for you and the club?
- Gem Gem
- 别 别 别
NERO: - Gem, Gem...
GEMMA: - No, no, no.
他得知道
He needs to know.
什么？
JAX: What?
检察官想让他把你交代出来
GEMMA: DA wanted
him to give you up.
他不愿意
He wouldn't.
但是他知道那个婊子不会罢休
But he also knew that that
bitch would keep coming.
所以他供出自己是枪的来源
So he gave himself up
as the gun source.
- 这是真的
- 你知道 这不要紧
JAX: - Is that true?
NERO: - Hey, you know, it-it didn't matter.
我正要做这笔交易的时候 我的律师
By the time I was gonna make
this deal, my lawyer found out
发现了警长们从Toric的房间里取得证据
that the sheriffs, they had
pulled evidence from Toric's
证实了是他杀的Erin
hotel room, proved that he was
the one that killed Erin.
所以Patterson放我走了
So, Patterson, she
had to let me go.
我不知道她咬的你这么紧
JAX: I didn't realize she
was bending you like that.
对 好吧
NERO: Yeah, well...
她不见血不罢休
she, uh, ain't gonna stop
until she draws blood, man.
是啊
JAX: Yeah.
好了 宝贝
NERO: Come on, babe.
你没事吧
BOBBY: You all right?
有些事
JAX: No, not really.
Nero说得对
Nero's right.
Patterson不会就此罢休
Patterson ain't gonna stop.
召集大家开堂会
Call everyone. Chapel.
我们要投票
We need to take a vote.
嗨 我找到Putner的地址了 兄弟
TIG: Hey. We got an
address for Putner, man.
就离这里几条街
It's actually a few
blocks from here.
- 在Willow Gulch
- 好 我们走
- It's Willow Gulch.
JAX: - All right, let's go.
好 好 走吧
TIG: All right.
All right, come on.
(knocking)
(small dog barks)
- 你是Putner
- 是的
JAX: - You Putner?
GARY: - Yeah.
- 我是Jax Teller 我在找你的孩子
JAX: Jax Teller. I'm
looking for your kid.
我也在找 我听说了
GARY: Me, too. Heard
about what happened.
- 你是追她的那个人？
- 是的
- You the one who chased her?
JAX: - Yeah.
我没伤害她
I didn't hurt her.
我只是想知道答案
I just want some answers.
我明白 进来吧
GARY: I get that. Come on in.
Brooke 有些麻烦
Brooke's got some stuff.
焦虑 两极性格
Anxiety, bipolar.
他妈妈也这样
Her mom had it, too.
你知道我是谁吗
JAX: Do you know who I am?
知道
GARY: Yeah.
你觉得这是他袭击我们的原因吗
JAX: Is that why she
attacked us, do you think?
因为我老爸
Because of my dad?
这周很艰难
GARY: Been a rough week.
我的房子没了
I lost the house.
我们在打包东西
We've been packing shit up.
发现了很多他妈妈的照片
Came across a lot of
photos of her mom.
在报纸上看到她死了的新闻
Found the newspaper
article about her death.
起初她以为是你爸引起的连带伤害杀死了她妈
First time she realized your dad
caused the pileup that killed her mom.
我猜 在她混乱的小脑袋里 他怪罪你们
I guess, in her messy little
brain, she blames you guys.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没事 我明白
JAX: No, I get it.
这是你妻子
That your wife?
是的 我和Emily
GARY: Yeah. Me and Emily.
怎么了
Why?
她看起来眼熟
JAX: She looks familiar.
我知道 我之前也这样
GARY: I know.
Happens to me, too.
看别人像他
I see her a lot...
in other people.
那你知道你的孩子可能在哪吗
JAX: So you got any idea
where your kid might be?
我不清楚
GARY: I don't know.
即便她一般都会回家
She always comes home, though.
我会找她谈出个端倪
I'll talk to her and
straighten this out.
好的
JAX: Yeah, okay.
我会赔偿你们的损失
GARY: We'll pay for the damage.
没事 别担心
JAX: No, don't worry about that.
谢谢
GARY: Thank you.
嗨
JAX: Hey.
(kids chattering)
过来
TARA: Here you go.
嗨 接着这个 准备好了?
Hey, take that.
Ready?
真棒
Awesome.
谢谢
Thank you.
等下见
I'll see you later.
你在找Jax
You looking for Jax?
不 其实 我想和你谈谈
NERO: No. I was, uh, hoping
I could talk to you.
当然好
TARA: Sure.
这个是因为天生的缺陷
NERO: Is that for his,
uh, birth defect?
是的 心律不齐
TARA: Yeah. Heart arrhythmia.
看起来对他们什么影响
NERO: Doesn't seem
to slow him down.
是的 没影响
TARA: No, it doesn't.
你怎么样
NERO: How are you feeling?
还行
TARA: Fine.
我想你来这不是为了看看我家里人的健康问题
I'm assuming you're not just here to
check on the health of my family.
其实我是的
NERO: Actually, I am.
情绪健康
Emotional health.
嗯 我们在努力度过这段时期
TARA: Well, we're all
getting through it.
不是所有人
NERO: Not everyone.
医生 你不把我当做一个恶人
Doc, you know, you don't strike me
as being a malicious kind of person.
我确信无论你和Gemma之间发生什么
I'm sure whatever it was that
happened between you and
你做了你认为对的事情
Gemma, you did what you
thought was right.
Gemma袭击了我 导致了流产
TARA: Gemma attacked me.
Caused a miscarriage.
没错 我想我在请求你能不能换个角度想想
NERO: Right. I guess I'm asking if you could
take another look at what's been done.
你们的家庭正在分裂
The rip it's causing
in your family.
你没资格将我的家庭 你不了解我
TARA: You don't get to weigh in
on my family. You don't know me.
对 我不了解 但是我了解Gemma 你也是
NERO: No, I don't, but I do
know Gemma and so do you.
她不会就这样放手
She's not gonna lay
down for this.
也许我们能找个双方妥协的办法
Maybe we could find some
kind of middle ground here.
因为 如果不这样 对双方都不好
'Cause if not... this is not
gonna end up well for anyone.
包括你 你知道和他在一起的男人都什么下场
TARA: Including you. You see what
happens to the men she's with.
一个丈夫死了 一个在监狱
One husband dead,
another in jail.
是的 你知道 这就是生活（越狱名言）
NERO: Yeah, well, you
know, that's the life.
不对 这是因为那个女人 她杀了John Teller
TARA: No, it's the wife!
She killed John Teller!
也许同样会对Clay下手
Probably would've done
the same to Clay.
你想有个好结果
You want it to end well?
我建议你在你死之前抽身
I suggest you get out now
before you end up dead, too.
(door opens)
他就是那个在教堂里捣乱的人
TROUT: Is he the one who
flipped out in the chapel?
是的 医生 他现在稳定了 没事
ORDERLY: Yeah, Doc.
He's calm now. He's secure.
好的 交给我吧 你去6号房帮帮Nance
TROUT: Okay. I got it.
Go help Nance in six.
Tanner还有出戏要演
Tanner had another episode.
该死 好的吧
ORDERLY: Shit. Yeah, okay.
(orderly sighs)
(door closes)
(lock clicks)
- 你是Morrow
- 是的
TROUT: - You Morrow?
CLAY: - Yeah.
在下次探班之前你有40分钟时间
TROUT: You got 40 minutes
till the next rotation.
你要是被抓了还把我供出来 我会把你拉到这来捆了你
You get caught, you give me up,
I'll pull you in here, strap you down,
用三倍量的氯丙嗪炸了你的脑子
fry your brain with a
triple dose of Thorazine.
Hippocratic誓言里面有这句话?
（Hippocratic oath是外国医生上岗前的宣誓誓言）
CLAY: What part of the
Hippocratic oath is that?
如果你的爱尔兰猪朋友不付
足够我退休的钱
TROUT: Same part that says
your mick friends don't pay
一样炸了你
enough for me to take a fall.
(door closes)
(lock clicks)
(dialing)
(elevator bell dings)
Murphy女士 Knowles医生10分钟前找你
NURSE: Ms. Murphy, from
Dr. Knowles, ten minutes ago.
谢谢
MARGARET: Thank you.
Tara
Tara?
(gasps)
她回家了
GEMMA: She went home.
我立马就能交保安来
MARGARET: I can have
security here in an instant.
没必要
GEMMA: No need.
我们谈谈接下来的事情
I debated how to do this.
在我看来 你对我做的事情
The way I feel...
what you did to me...
我完全可以拧开你苍白的嗓子
I could squeeze the swallow out
of that pale white throat.
但是 那只会增加你的正义感
But that would just give you a
greater sense of righteousness.
所以我不会那样做
So let me tell you
what's gonna happen now.
我会拿着记录Tara怀孕流产的
I'm gonna take those medical
records documenting Tara's
医药档案
pregnancy and her miscarriage,
然后交给医院董事会
and I'll present them
to the hospital board.
让他们知道你这个新生的主管是个骗子
Let them know that their Neonatal
administrator is a bit of a grifter.
那样的话是我的证词对你的证词
MARGARET: It would be
my word against yours.
我就想知道这么多
GEMMA: That's all I
needed to know.
谢谢你 红发妹
Thanks, Red.
你什么意思
MARGARET: What does that mean?
意思是如果怀孕是真的你就会说
GEMMA: It means if the pregnancy was
legit, you would've told me that
这些文档是真的 还会说我疯了
those documents were real
and called me crazy.
- 你证明不了什么
- 哦 我不需要证明
MARGARET: - You can't prove anything.
GEMMA: - Oh, I don't need to prove it.
我只是需要一个比吸毒者更可靠的来源来告诉我儿子
I just needed a more reliable source
than a junkie to share with my son.
他会证明的
He's gonna be the
one to prove it.
等他证明了 我马上告诉你 红发妹
And when he does, I'll tell
you right now, Red...
那时候就没有保安能保证你安全了
there won't be enough security
in this state to keep you safe.
(door opens, closes)
同意
JUICE: Yea.
Proxied West和Montez都同意
QUINN: Proxied West and
Montez, they're a yea.
同意
BOBBY: Yea.
RAT BOY: Yea.
同意
TIG: Yea.
HAPPY: Yea.
好的
JAX: All right.
我会去提这个条件
I'll go make the offer.
把他带进来
PATTERSON: Send him in.
请坐
Have a seat.
(door closes)
我得说我很惊讶你会坐在我对面
I must say, I'm rather surprised
to see you sitting across from me.
我比你还惊讶
JAX: No more
surprised than I am.
你来干嘛
PATTERSON: So why are you here?
(Jax sighs)
我的父亲 John Teller创办了混乱之子
JAX: Sons of Anarchy was started
by my father, John Teller.
他一直希望有一个合法的帮会
He always wanted a
legitimate club.
以死来追求
Died pursuing that.
我没兴趣听历史课
PATTERSON: I'm not in a
mood for a history lesson.
你为什么不说重点 Teller先生
Why don't you get
to it, Mr. Teller.
我来这是为了给你一个条件
JAX: I'm here to
make you an offer.
给我
PATTERSON: To make me...
(laughs)
哇
Wow.
你真有种 小子
You really have some balls, kid.
我还有卖KG-9的爱尔兰人
JAX: I also have an
Irishman who sells KG-9s.
爱尔兰共和军
PATTERSON: IRA?
真-爱尔兰共和军
JAX: Real IRA.
爱尔兰天主革命的现任国王们
Current kings of the Irish
Catholic revolution.
那你能给我什么
PATTERSON: So what
are you offering?
Gaalan O'Shay
JAX: Gaalan O'Shay.
你可以让联邦调查局查一下
You can check with the feds.
他是条大鱼
He's a big win.
我会把他和一次运的枪都给你
I will deliver him with
a shipment of guns.
一次性
Open and shut.
那么你什么时候如何给我这条大鱼
PATTERSON: And when and how would
you deliver this "big win"?
10天之内
JAX: It'll happen in
the next ten days.
如何是我管的事情
The "how" is my job.
这提议真大胆
PATTERSON: It's a very
bold proposition.
那你告诉我你的好处
So why don't you tell me
what's in it for you.
帮会对于枪支指控的豁免权
JAX: Immunity for the
MC for all gun charges.
过去和现在的
Past and present.
我想要一个合法的帮会
I want a legitimate club.
有人想攻击我们并且毁了我们生意伙伴的话可没法实现
That can't happen while people
try to crush us, ruining all of
的话可没法实现
our business relationships.
在Stockton放我们一马
Let us breathe in Stockton.
我们不会犯法而且不再有暴力
We won't break the law
and the violence stops.
就这些
PATTERSON: That's it?
如果你觉得你能给我爱尔兰共和军
If you thought you could
deliver the IRA,
那我觉得你应该有个私人请求
then I figure you would at least
also have a personal request.
我有
JAX: I do.
你要重新看一下Tara的案子
You need to look at
Tara's case again.
是Toric制造了不存在的案件
Toric was the one connecting
the dots that didn't exist.
Tara不知道Otto会对那个护士做什么
Tara had no idea what Otto
was gonna do to that nurse.
我们都明白这点
We both know that.
我知道的和我能证明的大不一样
PATTERSON: What I know and what I
can prove rarely come together.
那么
So...
我应该相信你能办到这些
I'm supposed to expedite all
of these things on good faith?
假设这都是真的
Just assume it's all real?
你不需要相信我
JAX: You don't need faith.
做好准备就行了
Just have everything ready to go,
然后给我们点空间行动
and give us the space
to put it in motion.
如果爱尔兰人认为我们被跟踪了 就全完了
If the Irish think we're being
tailed, this whole thing implodes.
我告诉你Gaalan和枪在哪
I'll tell you where to
find Gaalan and the guns.
然你和你团伙就溜走了
PATTERSON: And you and your
crew, you just skate away
不受到一点牵连
without so much as a
slap on the wrist?
等到他们完蛋的时候你也可以牵连我们
JAX: You can slap my wrists
until they're bloody, lady.
我他妈才不关心这个
I don't give a shit.
我再给你一个与你的薪水不相符的机会
I'm giving you a win well
above your pay grade.
你带着你的罪恶感别趟这滩浑水
You get your devil and you punch
your ticket out of this cesspool.
你留着你的正义感
So let's not get too
lost in righteousness.
我是不守法的人渣 你是正义的支柱
I'm the scumbag outlaw, and
you're the pillar of justice.
而且我们都不想在镜子里看到对方
And neither one of us likes looking
at ourselves in the mirror.
成交?
Do we have a deal?
如果10天之内没你的消息
PATTERSON: If I don't hear
from you within ten days...
接下来的7个月我会在这个办公室里
I will spend the last seven
months in this office making
用法律让你痛不欲生
your life as miserable
as the law allows.
还有你妻子
And your wife...
他会带在监狱里知道你的孩子高中毕业
she will be in jail until your boys
graduate from high school.
好
JAX: Okay.
(door opens, closes)
(Unser chattering)
(motorcycles approaching)
- 我们会关注消息
- 好
HAPPY: - We'll check messages.
JAX: - Fine.
暴躁叔 你有钥匙吗
HAPPY: Uncle T, you got the key?
- 好 好
- 多谢
UNSER: - Hey. All right.
JAX: - Thanks.
- 就在这
UNSER: You got it. Right here.
想买吗 我们在跳楼价促销中
JAX: Want to buy it?
We're having a fire sale.
该死 你该庆幸没人受伤
OSWALD: Shit. You're
lucky no one was hurt.
- 是啊
- 你准备怎么办
JAX: - Yeah.
OSWALD: - What're you gonna do?
看看保险能给多少
JAX: Waiting for the insurance
to come up with a number.
很明显C-4不在保单上
Apparently we didn't
have C-4 coverage.
你需要什么吗
OSWALD: What do you need?
我们不用你的仓库了
JAX: We're done with
your lumber warehouse.
不做军火生意了
Moving out of guns.
来得晚总比不来好
OSWALD: Better late
than never, I guess.
- 就这事
- 不是
- That it?
JAX: - No.
有个伙计在磨坊给你工作
There's a guy that works
for you at the mill.
Gary Putner.
啊 不错的工人 他怎么了
OSWALD: Yeah. Good worker.
What about him?
他的房子要没了
JAX: He's losing his house.
只有他一个人有收入
He's got a single income.
孩子也有些问题
Kid with some problems.
我希望你能帮帮他
I'd like it if you
could help him.
我是他老板不是他慈祥的教母
OSWALD: I'm his employer,
not his fairy godmother.
别这样 Oswald 你有个货代公司
JAX: Come on, Oswald, you got a
credit union and a loan company.
别让这个人连家都没有
Don't let the guy
lose his home.
我会帮他但是我们现在麻烦一堆
I'd help him, but we're tapped.
你为什么关心这个
OSWALD: Why's this
so important to you?
不知道
JAX: I don't know.
这样 我欠你一个人情
Hey, I'll owe you one.
我在竞选市长
OSWALD: I am throwing
my hat in for mayor.
Hale 没戏了
Hale's done.
我也许需要帮助
I may need some favors.
随便什么
JAX: Whatever you need.
我再联系你
OSWALD: I'll be in touch.
(cell phone ringing)
(engine starts)
嗨
Hey.
干嘛
What?
冷静点 宝贝
Babe, calm down.
谢谢
CLAY: Thanks.
没事
TROUT: No problem.
你有40分钟时间
You got 40 minutes.
我们知道规矩
GUARD: We know the drill.
治疗开始
TROUT: Let the therapy begin.
(door closes)
(lock clicks)
GUARD: Sermon's over, shithead.
(grunting)
(quiet chatter)
嗨 兄弟 Jax在厨房等着你
HAPPY: Hey, man. Jax needs
you in the kitchen.
- 什么事
- 检察官那有新消息
NERO: - What's up?
QUINN: - Update on the DA.
- 我和Tara聊过了
- 该死
JAX: - I talked to Tara.
NERO: - Shit.
我告诉你了我的家事不归你管
JAX: I told you my
family is off-limits.
我只想听听她怎么说
NERO: I just wanted
to hear her side.
这就是为什么你说她骗人
JAX: Is that why you
called her a liar?
什么 我没叫她
NERO: What? I didn't call her no...
你说她是操纵别人的婊子
JAX: You said she was
a manipulative bitch!
如果她这么和你说的 那她就是
NERO: If she told you that,
well, then I guess she is.
(grunting)
好吧 来啊
All right, come on.
(clattering)
(Nero and Jax grunting)
你现在可不想进去 老妈
QUINN: You don't want to go
back there right now, ma'am.
听着 他们因为我可能会受伤
GEMMA: Look, they're gonna
hurt each other 'cause of me.
拜托 分开他们
Come on, break it up.
Hap 求你了
Hap, please.
走
HAPPY: Let's go.
(grunting)
Jax Jax 好啦 别打了
Jax, Jax, come on, break it up!
停下 停手 Jax
GEMMA: Stop it!
Stop it, Jackson!
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦
HAPPY: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
天啊
GEMMA: Oh, Jesus.
对不起 老妈
NERO: I'm sorry, mama.
我不想 我不想事情变成这样
I didn't want... I didn't
want it to happen like this.
没什么对不起的
JAX: Don't be sorry.
她就是我们互相厮杀的原因
She's reason we're trying
to kill each other.
兄弟 你根本不知道她为你做了什么
NERO: Man, you got no idea
what she's done for you!
我知道的够多了 Nero
JAX: I know everything
I need to know, Nero!
是吗 那探视Clay的事情呢
NERO: Oh, yeah? What about the
little conjugal with Clay?
- 别
- 不 不 不 老妈
GEMMA: - Don't!
NERO: - No, no, no, mama!
你告诉他我 我做了什么
You told him what-what I did.
现在他要知道
Now he needs to know...
他要知道你为他做了什么
he needs to know
what you've done for him.
那么Clay那边怎么了
JAX: So what happened with Clay?
监狱里的警卫
NERO: The guards from the cell.
他们强迫你妈妈和Clay做爱
They forced your mother
to have sex with Clay.
然后他们看着
While they watched.
他们还打飞机
While they got off.
没关系
GEMMA: It doesn't matter.
都结束了
It's done.
没有 妈
JAX: No, Mom.
我刚刚和 Margaret谈了谈
GEMMA: I just talked to Margaret...
她证实了你拒绝相信的事情
who confirmed what
you refuse to believe.
亲爱的 那都是谎言
Honey, it was all a lie.
怀孕 流产
The pregnancy, the miscarriage.
Tara想离开 Jax
Tara wants out, Jax.
离开你 离开帮会 离开Charming
You, the club, Charming.
她正准备离婚 她还要把你的儿子们带走
She's filing for divorce, and she's
gonna take your boys away from you.
远离我们所有人
From all of us.
亲爱的 对不起
And, honey, I'm sorry.
我也爱她
I love her, too.
但是这是事实
But this is the truth.
如果她不告诉你
And if she's not gonna tell you,
你要去找你一个愿意告诉你的人
you need to find someone who will.
谢谢你能来
UNSER: Thanks for coming.
嗯 听起来有重要事
LOWEN: Yeah. Sounded important.
是的 关于Tara和孩子们的事情
UNSER: It is. It's about
Tara and the kids.
来 请到这边来
Here, come this way, please.
过来
Come on.
你 请坐
Just... have a seat.
我马上回来
I-I'll be right back.
(lock clicks)
坐下
JAX: Sit... down.
我不想伤害你Lowen
I don't want to have
to hurt you, Lowen.
我要问你几个问题
I need to ask you
some questions.
别这样 求你了
LOWEN: Please don't do this.
Tara在和我离婚吗
JAX: Is Tara divorcing me?
回答我
Answer me!
是的
LOWEN: Yes.
带走孩子们
JAX: And taking my sons?
还有怀孕
The pregnancy...
- 我不
- 是不是
LOWEN: - I didn't...
JAX: - Was it...!
是不是谎言
Was it a lie?
是的 我认为是
LOWEN: Yes, I think so.
为什么
JAX: Why?
抚养权
LOWEN: Custody waiver.
Gemma得不到孩子们
So Gemma couldn't
take the boys.
请别伤害我
Please don't hurt me.
滚
JAX: Get out.
- Tara只是在
- 滚
LOWEN: - Tara was just trying...
JAX: - Get out!
(crickets chirping)
知道你需要的事情了
UNSER: You get what you needed?
(car door closes)
嗯
JAX: Yeah.
(engine starts)
你保证过的 孩子
UNSER: You made me
a promise, son.
没人受伤
Nobody gets hurt.
我知道
JAX: Yeah.
(car drives away)
Nobody gets hurt.
(dialing)
(line ringing)
(phone ringing)
你好
TARA: Hello.
Tara 我是Ally Lowen
LOWEN: Tara, it's Ally Lowen.
你为什么去找Tara
GEMMA: Why'd you go to Tara?
我不想这样
It's not what I wanted.
我不知道
NERO: I don't know.
我认为如果她知道她现在造成的伤害
I thought maybe if she knew all the
damage that was being done...
看来事与愿违了
GEMMA: I guess that backfired.
是啊
NERO: Yeah.
她说了些你的事情
She had some things
to say about you.
她当然会说
GEMMA: I'm sure she did.
关于John的事情
NERO: About John.
她说什么了
GEMMA: What'd she tell you?
你杀了他
NERO: That you killed him.
是真的吗
Any truth to that?
(Gemma sighs)
John试着让帮会脱离军火交易
GEMMA: John was trying to
get the club out of guns.
当时就想现在这么紧张
It was as tense
then as it is now.
他去了Belfast好几次
He was making trips
back and forth to Belfast,
想和爱尔兰人和解
trying to make it
right with the Irish.
然后他爱上了一个人
He fell in love with someone.
Maureen Ashby.
他哥哥是个牧师 John的朋友
Brother was a priest,
friend of John's,
帮助他与爱尔兰共和军和解
helping broker a peaceful
transition with the IRA.
我发现了
I found out.
开始和Clay在一起
Started spending time with Clay.
我的Thomas死的时候John不在身边
My Thomas died when John was
away on one of those trips.
所以他回来的时候我不是太友好
And I wasn't kind
when he got home.
失去孩子的痛苦和愤怒都发泄在他身上
The pain and anger of losing my
baby, I made sure it landed on him.
他崩溃了
He came undone after that.
和爱尔兰共和军的谈判也瓦解了
Talks with the IRA fell apart.
Clay和McGee重新揽起了生意
Clay and McGee put them
back together again.
另一方面
In the other direction.
为帮会稳固了军火交易
Solidified the gun
trade for the club.
使他们开始掌权
Made them players.
但是JT
But JT...
他开始写
he started writing in this...
日记 手稿
this journal, a manuscript.
那是血淋漓的忏悔
It was a bleeding confession,
质疑他所有的决定
questioning all his choices,
后悔他为SAMCRO做的一切
regretting everything
he'd ever done in SAMCRO.
他不再关心帮会
He stopped caring
about the club.
他的家庭
About his family.
而且那时很危险
And it was a
dangerous time here.
与Mayan的战争
Mayan war.
两帮调查局对帮会紧追不舍
Feds infiltrating MCs.
所有人都害怕了
Everyone was scared.
JT是最弱的一环节
JT was a weak link.
你没回答我的问题
NERO: You didn't
answer my question.
我没杀他
GEMMA: I didn't kill him.
但是我知道他必须死
But I knew it had to be done.
就像你知道Arcadio必须死一样
The same way you knew it had
to be done with Arcadio.
我们以这个原则判定生死
We live and die by that code.
现在我知道 当时我也知道
I know it now, and
I knew it then.
而且我没有对我爱的男人隐瞒观点
And I did not hide my opinion from
the man I'd fallen in love with.
我赞成Clay杀死John Teller
I gave my blessing for
Clay to kill John Teller.
我没对任何人讲过这件事
I've never told that to anyone.
包括我儿子
Including my son.
(engine stops)
(electronic doorbell chimes)
天哪 Jackie 你没事吧
CHIBS: Jesus Christ, Jackie.
You okay?
我没事
JAX: I'm all right.
你的小女朋友来了
CHIBS: Your little
girlfriend's here.
想说说话
Wants to talk.
拿扳手的那个
JAX: Girl with the wrench?
对 她还没说什么
BOBBY: Yeah. She
hasn't said much.
除了说她要见你
Except that she
needs to see you.
让我单独和她谈谈
JAX: Let me talk to her alone.
她没带武器
BOBBY: She ain't packing.
走
Go.
好吧 起立 到楼上去
CHIBS: All right, get up.
Upstairs.
你也来 笛子先生
You, too, Mr. Kazoo.
(Chuck playing kazoo)
那个吹笛子的人真有意思
BROOKE: Guy with the kazoo's
pretty interesting.
我们在门前了篮子里找到他的
JAX: We found him in a
basket on our doorstep.
他怎么了
BROOKE: What happened?
被扳手打的
JAX: Got hit with a pipe wrench.
好吧 对
BROOKE: Yeah, I'm...
对不起砸了你的窗户
I'm sorry about the window...
还有车
and the bike.
我和你爸爸谈过了
JAX: I talked to your dad.
我知道
BROOKE: I know.
我
I-I'm...
我不太清楚发生了什么
I'm not really
sure what happened.
我是说 我看到那篇报道
I mean, I-I found the article,
然后我知道你们搬到这来了
and I knew you
guys moved in here.
我有些
I-I've got some...
有些混事 你知道的 在
some shit going
on, you know, in...
在我脑子里
in my head.
我们都有
JAX: We all do.
我爸爸
BROOKE: My dad...
我爸爸说 你 你和他老板谈了谈
my dad said
you-you talked with his boss.
他会帮助我们留下房子
He's gonna help us
keep the house.
在我对你做了这些之后你为什么还这样做
Why would you do that
after what I did?
我就是这样对当妈的说对不起的
JAX: It's just my way of
saying sorry to a mother.
谢谢你
BROOKE (crying): Thank you.
愿你的梦
TARA: ♪ May your dreams ♪
在黑暗中
♪ bring you peace ♪
给你带来祥和
♪ in the darkness ♪
愿你的头在雨中
♪ May your head rise over ♪
高昂
♪ the rain ♪
愿天上的光
♪ May the light from above ♪
永远指引着爱
♪ always lead you to love ♪
愿你能偎依在
♪ May you stay in the arms ♪
天使的怀中
♪ of the angels ♪
愿你在阴影中
♪ May you always be brave ♪
永远勇敢
♪ in the shadows ♪
直到阳光
♪ till the sun shines ♪
再次照耀着你
♪ upon you again ♪
听着我心中的
♪ Hear this prayer ♪
祷告
♪ in my heart ♪
我们永不分离
♪ and we'll ne'er be apart ♪
愿你能偎依在
♪ May you stay in the arms ♪
天使的怀中
♪ of the angels ♪
愿你能在树林中
♪ May you hear every song ♪
聆听每一支歌
♪ in the forest ♪
如果你
♪ And if ever you lose ♪
迷失了方向
♪ your own way ♪
聆听我
♪ hear my voice ♪
如拂过林间
♪ like a breeze ♪
微风般的声音
♪ whisper soft through the trees ♪
愿你能偎依在
♪ May you stay in the arms ♪
天使的怀中
♪ of the angels ♪
愿你成长为
♪ May you grow up to
stand as a man, love ♪
一个以家族
♪ with the pride of your family ♪
为荣的男人
♪ and name ♪
当你低下头
♪ When you lay down your head ♪
卧床休息时
♪ for to rest in your bed ♪
愿你能偎依在
TARA: ♪ May you stay ♪
天使的怀中
♪ in the arms of the angels ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01 汉化Derekwxt
www.addic7ed.com